一，短对话理解。
你将听到五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题，请在每小题所给的。
三个选项中选出一个最佳选项。
每段对话读两遍。
1. 2. George, do you like playing basketball or volleyball?
Neither, I like playing football.
George, do you like playing basketball or volleyball?
3. Tom, how do you go to school every day?
I usually walk, but this morning I took a bus because of the bad weather.
4. going to be late
4. Hurry up, Jack.
We're going to be late for class.
Don't worry, it starts at 8.30.
We still have 15 minutes.
5. Anything Anything stomach?
stomach? 5. Anything
5. Anything stomach?
5. Anything wrong with stomach?
Nothing serious. Take the medicine three times a day.
Come back and have a check again next Monday.
5. wrong with my stomach?
5. serious. Take the medicine three times a day.
Come back and have a check again next Monday.
二，长对话理解。
你将听到两段对话，每段对话后有几个小题，请在每小题所给的
三个选项中选出一个最佳选项。
每段对话读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答第六七题。
5. wrong my stomach?
5. wrong 5.
wrong with stomach?
Can I help you, sir?
I'm looking for a coat for myself.
What color do you like?
I'd like something gray or black.
What about this one?
It matches your white shirt.
I like it.
May I try it on?
Of course. This way, please.
Can I help you, sir?
I'm looking for a coat for myself.
What color do you like?
I'd like something gray or black.
What about this one?
It matches your white shirt.
I like it.
May I try it on?
Of course. This way, please.
听下面一段对话，回答第八至十题。
Great. are you going to do this weekend?
I'm going for a picnic with my cousin.
What about you?
I'm planning to get a part -time job.
A part -time job?
Yes. I want to buy a scarf for my father and a watch for my mother.
Also, I need a hat.
A nice plan, but it might be better to put it off till this summer vacation.
You'll have more time then.
Good idea. I will.
Haven't got sunny days for so long.
I wonder when the rain will stop.
The weather report says it will be sunny this weekend.
Great. What are you going to do this weekend?
I'm going for a picnic with my cousin.
What about you?
I'm planning to get a part -time job.
part -time job?
Yes. I want to buy a scarf for my father and a watch for my mother.
Also, I need a hat.
A nice plan, but it might be better to put it off till this summer vacation.
You'll have more time then.
Good idea. I will.
三，短文理解。
你将听到一篇短文，短文后有五个小题，请根据短文内容，在每小题所给
三个选项中选出一个最佳选项。
短文读两遍。
Last month, our school held a speech competition.
It was about the development of our motherland.
It lasted three days.
My classmate, Li took part in it for our class.
Before the competition, he was nervous because he didn't know how to prepare for it.
Our English teacher told him to search for information on the Internet.
Thanks to his suggestion, Li got to know more about the development of our
motherland. He was surprised at her great changes and felt proud.
He spent five days preparing for it and finally won first prize.
Li Hua was very happy about the result.
Last month, our school held a speech competition.
It was about the development of our motherland.
It lasted three days.
My classmate, Li took part in it for our class.
Before the competition, he was nervous because he didn't know how to prepare for it.
Our English teacher told him to search for information on the Internet.
Thanks to his suggestion, Li got to know more about the development of our
motherland. He was surprised at her great changes and felt proud.
He spent five days preparing for it and finally won first prize.
Li Hua was very happy about the result.
Thanks Thank you watching.
四、信息转换。
你将听到一篇短文，请根据短文内容写出下面表格中所缺的单词，每空仅
填一词。
短文读两遍。
There are many ways to show love.
You may give small gifts like cards, flowers, and candies.
That connects you and others.
Sometimes you may show love by encouraging others.
Words like I believe in you or you can make it will give them hope.
In some situations, you may show love by offering to help with something.
That means you are a warm person.
What's more, you may ask for advice to show love.
That makes people feel you trust them.
You may give small gifts like cards, flowers, and candies.
That connects you and others.
Sometimes you may show love by encouraging others.
Words like I believe in you or you can make it will give them hope.
In some situations, you may show love by offering to help with something.
That means you are a warm person.
What's more, you may ask for advice to show love.
That makes people feel you trust them.
Thank you for watching.